Guide to the Religious Education Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Financial and Promotional Records, Series IX
  - Committee records
    - Jewish Appeals, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 1484)
    - Protestant Laymen Appeals, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 1485)
    - Catholic Laymen Appeals, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 1486)
    - Catholic/Protestant Appeals, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 1487)
    - Records, 1956-1959 (Box 128, Folder 1488-1491)
    - Membership Promotion, 1960 (Box 128, Folder 1492)
    - Membership Promotion/Financial, 1961 (Box 128, Folder 1493)
    - General, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 1494)
    - Membership Promotion/Development Committee, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1495)
    - Development Committee, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1496-1497)
    - Development Campaign, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1498)
    - Development Campaign - Finance, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1499)
    - Membership Promotion (Catholic Teachers), 1963 (Box 129, Folder 1500)
    - Development Committee, 1964 (Box 129, Folder 1501)
    - General, 1965-1969 (Box 129, Folder 1502-1506)
    - Brochures, 1970s (Box 129, Folder 1507)
    - Sustaining Program/General Committee records, 1971 (Box 129, Folder 1508)
    - Finance/Membership, 1971-1972 (Box 129, Folder 1509)
    - Thanksgiving Appeal/General, 1974 (Box 129, Folder 1510)
    - General, 1975-1976 (Box 129, Folder 1511-1512)
    - 70th Anniversary Appeal, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 1513)
    - 75th Anniversary Appeal, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 1514)
    - Records, 1978-1979 (Box 129, Folder 1515-1517)
    - Nathan Fund, 1978 (Box 130, Folder 1518)
    - Records, 1979-1980 (Box 130, Folder 1519-1520)
  - Fundraisers
    - Albright, Charles W. (Box 130, Folder 1521)
    - Borowitz, Rabbi Eugene (Box 130, Folder 1522)
    - Chicago Lay Contributors (Box 130, Folder 1523-1524)
    - Driscoll, Mrs. Walter B. (Box 130, Folder 1525)
    - Freehof, Rabbi Solomon (Box 130, Folder 1526)
    - Gamble, Mrs. Sidney (Box 130, Folder 1527)
    - Gamoran, Emanuel (Box 130, Folder 1528)
    - Gibbs, Emily (Box 130, Folder 1529)
    - Gordon, Rabbi Albert (Box 130, Folder 1530)
    - Greenberg, Rabbi Simon Fundraisers (Box 130, Folder 1531)
    - Hartnett, Robert C. (Box 130, Folder 1532)
    - Heinz, Mrs. Clifford (Box 130, Folder 1533)
    - Hoey, Jane M. (Box 130, Folder 1534)
    - Hunter, David (Box 130, Folder 1535)
    - Johnson, F. Ernest (Box 130, Folder 1536)
    - Koob, Father Allen (Box 130, Folder 1537)
    - Krumm, John (Box 130, Folder 1538)
    - Lookstein, Rabbi Joseph (Box 130, Folder 1539)
    - Miller, Randolph C. (Box 130, Folder 1540)
    - Pilch, Judah (Box 131, Folder 1541)
    - Replogle, Fred (Box 131, Folder 1542)
    - Stephan, Edmund (Box 131, Folder 1543)
  - Funding sources
    - General lists (Box 131, Folder 1544)
    - Alcoa Foundation, 1962-1966 (Box 131, Folder 1545-1546)
    - Chicago based Foundations, 1957, 1961 (Box 131, Folder 1547)
    - Danforth Foundation, 1953-1963 (Box 131, Folder 1548)
    - Danielson Fund, 1956-1957 (Box 131, Folder 1549)
    - Dayton Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 131, Folder 1550)
    - Dodge Foundation, 1950-1975 (Box 131, Folder 1551-1552)
    - Ford Foundation, 1952-1963 (Box 131, Folder 1553)
    - General Service Foundation, 1952-1954 (Box 131, Folder 1554)
    - General Service Foundation, 1955-1972 (Box 132, Folder 1555)
    - Grant Foundation, 1954-1956 (Box 132, Folder 1556)
    - Hancock Church, 1956-1976 (Box 132, Folder 1557)
    - Hazen Foundation, 1953-1957 (Box 132, Folder 1558)
    - Inland Steel Foundation, 1961 (Box 132, Folder 1559)
    - Kennedy, Joseph Jr. Foundation, 1966 (Box 132, Folder 1560)
    - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1952-1967 (Box 132, Folder 1561-1564)
    - Lincoln Foundation, 1952-1955 (Box 132, Folder 1565)
    - Lindgren Foundation, 1959-1967 (Box 132, Folder 1566)
    - Meyerhoff Fund, 1978 (Box 132, Folder 1567)
    - New World Foundation, 1955-1962 (Box 132, Folder 1568)
    - New York Foundations, 1961-1962 (Box 132, Folder 1569)
    - Pew Memorial Trust, 1971-1974 (Box 132, Folder 1570)
    - Phillips Foundation, 1952-1970 (Box 133, Folder 1571-1572)
    - Pittsburgh Foundations, 1953, 1972 (Box 133, Folder 1573)
    - Playboy Foundation Appeals/Funding sources, 1971 (Box 133, Folder 1574)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1952-1955 (Box 133, Folder 1575)
    - St. Thomas Church, 1956-1971 (Box 133, Folder 1576)
    - Scaife Family Trusts, 1963 (Box 133, Folder 1577)
    - Sears, Roebuck and Co., 1947, 1957-1963 (Box 133, Folder 1578)
    - Stone Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 133, Folder 1579)
    - Trinity Church, 1957-1973 (Box 133, Folder 1580)
    - Wurzweiter Foundation, 1955-1976 (Box 133, Folder 1581)
    - Miscellaneous Foundation and Corporate Funding Sources, A - F (Box 133, Folder 1582)
    - Miscellaneous Foundation and Corporate Funding Sources, G - N (Box 133, Folder 1583)
    - Miscellaneous Foundation and Corporate Funding Sources, O - Z (Box 133, Folder 1584)
- Photographs, Series X
  - Presidents of R.E.A.
    - Charles Cuthbert Hall (1904-1905) (Box 135, Folder 1598)
    - William F. McDowell (1905-1906) (Box 135, Folder 1599)
    - William H. P. Faunce (1906-1907) (Box 135, Folder 1600)
    - Henry Churchill King (1907-1908) (Box 135, Folder 1601)
    - Francis G. Peabody (1908-1909) (Box 135, Folder 1602)
    - George Albert Coe (1909-1910) (Box 135, Folder 1603)
    - William Lawrence (1910-1911) (Box 135, Folder 1604)
    - James Hampton Kirkland (1911-1912) (Box 135, Folder 1605)
    - Harry Pratt Judson (1912-1913) (Box 135, Folder 1606)
    - Charles Franklin Thwing (1913-1914) (Box 135, Folder 1607)
    - Charles David Williams (1914-1915) (Box 135, Folder 1608)
    - George Black Stewart (1915-1916) (Box 135, Folder 1609)
    - Francis J. McConnell (1916-1917) (Box 135, Folder 1610)
    - Washington Gladden (1917-1918) (Box 135, Folder 1611)
    - Samuel A. Eliot (1918-1919) (Box 135, Folder 1612)
    - A. C. McGiffert (1919-1921) (Box 135, Folder 1613)
    - Theodore G. Soares (1912-1924) (Box 135, Folder 1614)
    - Donald J. Cowling (1924) (Box 135, Folder 1615)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Unidentified group photos (Box 135, Folder 1616)
    - Research Planning Workshop, Cornell University, 1961 Aug (Box 135, Folder 1617)